Finding Aid for Susan Wineberg papers, 1965-2009
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Collected Historical Materials
  - Ypsilanti
    - Downtown (Box 47)
    - Eastern Michigan University (Box 47)
    - Fire Museum (Box 47)
    - Freight House (Box 47)
    - Gardens (Box 47)
    - Historic District Commission (Box 47)
    - Historic District Commission Buildings (Box 48)
    - Heritage Festival (Box 48)
  - Michigan Townships
    - Dixboro (Box 48)
    - Freedom (Box 48)
    - Lima (Box 48)
    - Lodi (Box 48)
    - Lyndon (Box 48)
    - Manchester (Box 48)
    - Milan Northfield (Box 48)
    - Pittsfield, 3 folders (Box 48)
    - Salem (Box 49)
    - Saline, 4 folders (Box 49)
    - Scio, 3 folders (Box 49)
    - Sharon (Box 49)
    - Geer Study Committee (Box 49)
    - Superior, 3 folders (Box 49)
    - Sylvan (Box 49)
    - Township Islands (Box 49)
    - Webster (Box 50)
    - Whitmore Lake (Box 50)
    - Willow Run (Box 50)
    - York (Box 50)
    - Ypsilanti (Box 50)
  - Michigan Cites, Counties, and Landmarks
    - Alpena (Box 50)
    - Battle Creek (Box 50)
    - Berrien County (Box 50)
    - Brighton (Box 50)
    - Calhoun (Box 50)
    - Canton (Box 50)
    - Cass County (Box 50)
    - Charlevoix (Box 50)
    - Clarkston (Box 50)
    - Clinton (Box 50)
    - Cranbrook, 2 folders (Box 50)
    - Crawford (Box 50)
    - Dearborn (Box 50)
    - East Lansing (Box 50)
    - Emmet (Box 50)
    - Flint (Box 50)
    - Ford Village Industries (Box 50)
    - Franklin (Box 50)
    - Grand Rapids (Box 50)
    - Grass Lake (Box 50)
    - Greenfield Village/The Henry Ford, Dearborn (Box 50)
    - Green Oak Township (Box 50)
    - Grosse Pointe (Box 50)
    - Hamtramck (Box 50)
    - Hartland (Box 50)
    - Highland Park (Box 50)
    - Hillsdale (Box 50)
    - Holland (Box 50)
    - Howell (Box 50)
    - Huron (Box 50)
    - Ionia (Box 50)
    - Isabella (Box 50)
    - Jackson City (Box 50)
    - Kalamazoo (Box 50)
    - Lansing (Box 50)
    - Lake (Box 50)
    - Leelanau (Box 50)
    - Lenawee City (Box 50)
    - Livingston County (Box 50)
    - Ludington (Box 50)
    - Mackinac (Box 50)
    - Macomb (Box 50)
    - Manistee (Box 50)
    - Marshall (Box 50)
    - Mason (Box 50)
    - Meadowbrook Hall, Rochester (Box 50)
    - Mecosta (Box 50)
    - Midland (Box 50)
    - Monroe (Box 51)
    - Muskegon (Box 51)
    - Northville (Box 51)
    - Oakland County (Box 51)
    - Ottawa (Box 51)
    - Pickney (Box 51)
    - Plymouth (Box 51)
    - Pontiac (Box 51)
    - Rochester (Box 51)
    - Saginaw (Box 51)
    - St. Clair (Box 51)
    - St. Joseph County (Box 51)
    - Shiawassee (Box 51)
    - Tecumseh (Box 51)
    - Traverse Area (Box 51)
    - Traverse (Box 51)
    - Upper Peninsula (Box 51)
    - Waterloo Museum (Box 51)
    - Wayne County (Box 51)
  - Ann Arbor and Washtenaw County
    - Ann Arbor
      - Ann Arbor General, 2 folders (Box 51)
      - Barton Farms (Box 51)
      - Barlow Hills (Box 51)
      - 2426 Whitmore Lake (Box 51)
      - Dominos, The Settlement (Box 51)
      - Geddes Letters (Box 51)
      - Dhu Varren Farms (Box 51)
    - Washtenaw County
      - Augusta (Box 51)
      - Bridgewater (Box 51)
      - Chelsea, 2 folders (Box 51)
      - Chelsea, 2 folders (Box 52)
      - Cool Cities 2003 (Box 52)
      - Delhi (Box 52)
      - Dexter Historic District Commission (Box 52)
      - Dexter (Box 52)
      - Gordon Hall, Dexter (Box 52)
  - Detroit
    - Airport (Box 52)
    - Architects (Box 52)
    - Auto (Box 52)
    - Belle Isle (Box 52)
    - Black Historic Sites (Box 52)
    - Book Cadillac/Pickshells (Box 52)
    - Casinos (Box 52)
    - Churches (Box 52)
    - Deco (Box 52)
    - Downtown (Box 52)
    - Enns/Detroit Project (Box 52)
    - Institute of the Arts/Mocad (Box 52)
    - Fort Lernoult and Early Detroit (Box 52)
    - Eastern Market (Box 52)
    - Ephemera (Box 52)
    - Freer House (Box 52)
    - Heidelberg Project (Box 52)
    - Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 53)
    - Historic Buildings 2001 (Box 53)
    - Historic Buildings 2008 (Box 53)
    - Historic Districts (Box 53)
    - History (Box 53)
    - Indian Village/Pewabic (Box 53)
    - Lafayette Park (Box 53)
    - Madison Lenox (Box 53)
    - Palmer Park Historic District (Box 53)
    - Music (Box 53)
    - Poletown (Box 53)
    - Preservation (Box 53)
    - Redwood Station (Box 53)
    - Renaissance Center (Box 53)
    - Schools (Box 53)
    - Super Bowl 2006 (Box 53)
    - Stadiums (Box 53)
    - Theaters (Box 53)
    - Statler Hotel (Box 53)
    - Tiger Stadium (Box 53)
    - Wayne State University (Box 53)
    - Whitney (Box 53)
  - Michigan Jewish Community
    - Adler (Box 53)
    - Detroit Jews (Box 53)
    - Detroit Jews, 2 folders (Box 54)
    - Detroit Jewish History (Box 54)
    - Detroit Lost Synagogues (Box 54)
    - General (Box 54)
    - Jewish History (Box 54)
    - Holocaust Center, West Bloomfield, Michigan (Box 54)
    - Holocaust Memorial and Conference (Box 54)
    - Michigan Jews, 6 folders (Box 54)
    - Picketing at Beth Israel (Box 54)
    - Sherwin Wine, Humanistic Judaism (Box 54)
    - Ann Arbor
      - Jews, 3 folders (Box 55)
      - Raoul Wallenberg (Box 55)
  - Michigan General
    - 1960s (Box 55)
    - Agriculture (Box 55)
    - Amish (Box 55)
    - Andrews, Wayne 1982 (Box 55)
    - Archaeology (Box 55)
    - Architects and COPAR (Box 55)
    - Architecture (Box 55)
    - Auto Heritage Area (Box 55)
    - Barns, 2 folders (Box 55)
    - Bed and Breakfasts (Box 55)
    - Beer (Box 55)
    - Bibliography (Box 55)
    - Blacks (Box 55)
    - Bureau of History Tax Forms (Box 55)
    - Bridges (Box 55)
    - Businesses (Box 55)
    - Calendars (Box 55)
    - Capitol (Box 55)
    - Cemeteries (Box 55)
    - Centennial 1876 (Box 55)
    - Centennial Farms, 2 folders (Box 55)
    - Certified Local Government Program (Box 55)
    - Churches (Box 55)
    - Civil War (Box 55)
    - Clinton (Box 55)
    - Cobblestone (Box 55)
    - Cooking (Box 55)
    - Courthouses (Box 55)
    - Dairies (Box 55)
    - Easements (Box 56)
    - Farm Architecture (Box 56)
    - Food/Cookbooks (Box 56)
    - Food/Eating (Box 56)
    - Economy (Box 56)
    - Forests (Box 56)
    - Freedman's Progress 1915 (Box 56)
    - Furniture (Box 56)
    - Gardens (Box 56)
    - Germans (Box 56)
    - Governor's Awards (Box 56)
    - Historical Parks and State Historic Parks and Landmarks (Box 56)
    - History (Box 56)
    - Historic Preservation (Box 56)
    - Horticultural (Box 56)
    - Indians (Box 56)
    - Libraries (Carnegie) (Box 56)
    - Lighthouses (Box 56)
    - Log Cabins (Box 56)
    - M-60 (Box 56)
    - Maps (Box 56)
    - Major, Howard (Box 56)
    - Michigan Historic Preservation Network (Box 56)
    - Mills (Box 56)
    - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 56)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 56)
    - Museum/Library/Archives (Box 56)
    - Museums (Box 56)
    - National Historic Landmarks (Box 56)
    - Newspapers 1876 (Box 56)
    - Nurseries/People (Box 56)
    - Other Historic Districts (Box 56)
    - Oral History (Box 56)
    - Photography (Box 56)
    - Pickering, Ernest (Box 56)
    - Preservation Awards (Box 56)
    - Railroads (Box 56)
    - Recipes (Box 56)
    - Roads (Box 56)
    - Rural Preservation (Box 57)
    - Schools (Box 57)
    - Sculpture (Box 57)
    - Sesquicentennial 1987 (Box 57)
    - Stained Glass (Box 57)
    - State Historic Preservation Offices (Box 57)
    - State Register and Markers (Box 57)
    - Tax Credits (Box 57)
    - Women (Box 57)
    - Underground Railroad (Box 57)
  - University of Michigan
    - Aerial View (Box 57)
    - Alumni Building (Box 57)
    - Alumni (Box 57)
    - Angell Hall (Box 57)
    - Architecture Department (Box 57)
    - Art and Design (Box 57)
    - Nichols Arboretum (Box 57)
    - Burnham House move to art (Box 57)
    - Art Museum (Box 57)
    - Astronomy (Box 57)
    - Barbour/Waterman Gym (Box 57)
    - Bentley (Box 58)
    - Development (Box 58)
    - Diag (Box 58)
    - Dorms (Box 58)
    - Willard Hewey Dow Lab (Box 58)
    - Economics Building (Box 58)
    - Engineering Buildings (Box 58)
    - Faculty/Staff (Box 58)
    - Famous People (Box 58)
    - Fleming Building (Box 58)
    - Fresh Air Camp (Box 58)
    - Ford Public Policy (Box 58)
    - Frieze (Box 58)
    - Frats, Clubs, and Sororities
      - Frats (Box 58)
      - Nu Sigma Nu 1935 (Box 58)
    - Grounds (Box 59)
    - Haven Hall (Box 59)
    - Herbarium (Box 59)
    - Health Service (Box 59)
    - Hill Auditorium (Box 59)
    - League (Box 59)
    - Libraries (Box 59)
    - Libraries Miscellaneous (Box 59)
    - Life Sciences Institute, Palmer Commons, and USB (Box 59)
    - Lorch Hall (Box 59)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 59)
    - Museums Building (Box 59)
    - Music/Stearns (Box 59)
    - Natural Sciences (Kraus) (Box 59)
    - Near East Department (Box 59)
    - Radio WUOM (Box 59)
    - Randall Lab (Box 59)
    - "Red Scare," 1954 (Box 59)
    - Regents (Box 59)
    - Religion (Box 59)
    - Student Activities Building (Box 59)
    - Sculpture (Box 59)
    - Simpson Institute (Box 59)
    - Social Work (Box 59)
    - Sports (Box 59)
    - Sport Buildings (Box 60)
    - Michigan Stadium Expansion Controversy 2006-2008 (Box 60)
    - Football Stadium (Box 60)
    - Students (Box 60)
    - Student Publications (Box 60)
    - Tappan Hall (Box 60)
    - Theaters (Box 60)
    - Tisch Building (Box 60)
    - Touro (Box 60)
    - Union (Box 60)
    - Weill Hall (Box 60)
    - Victor Vaughn and Medical Science (Box 60)
    - Women (Box 60)
    - Sexual Harassment (Box 60)
    - North Campus (Box 60)
    - North Quad (Box 60)
    - NUBS (Box 60)
    - Neuroscience (Box 60)
    - Nursing (Box 60)
    - Observatory (Box 60)
    - "The Detroit Observatory" by Susan Wineberg (Box 60)
    - Observatory Lodge (Box 61)
    - Sandy Whitesell (Box 61)
    - Gay Delanghe (Box 61)
    - Parking (Box 61)
    - Perry School (Box 61)
    - Power Center (Box 61)
    - Power Plant (Box 61)
    - Presidents (Box 61)
    - President's House (Box 61)
    - Public Health (Box 61)
    - Publications (Box 61)
    - Rackham Building (Box 61)
    - Bookstore (Union Cellar) (Box 61)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 61)
    - Biomedical Research Building (Box 61)
    - Blacks (Box 61)
    - Buildings, Miscellaneous (Box 61)
    - Earliest buildings (Box 61)
    - Burton Tower (Box 61)
    - Business (Box 62)
    - Campus Views/Plans/History (Box 62)
    - Chemistry Building and Department (Box 62)
    - Clements Library (Box 62)
    - Construction (Box 62)
    - Dana Building, School of Natural Resources and Ecology (Box 62)
    - Dennison (Box 62)
    - Dental (Box 62)
    - Hillel (Box 62)
    - Historic Preservation (Box 62)
    - Historical Markers/Boulders (Box 62)
    - History (Box 62)
    - Charles Kendall Adams, "History of the University of Michigan," 1876 (Box 62)
    - Old Main Hospital (Box 62)
    - Hospital and Medical Buildings (Box 62)
    - First Hospitals (Box 62)
    - Homeopathic Hospital and ROTC North Hall (Box 62)
    - Catherine Street Hospitals (Box 62)
    - Medical School (and doctors) (Box 62)
    - Housing (Box 63)
    - Inglis House (Box 63)
    - Institute for Social Research (Box 63)
    - Kellogg Eye Center (Box 63)
    - Infrastructure Tunnels (Box 63)
    - Institute of the Humanities (Box 63)
    - Judaic Studies (Box 63)
    - Kelsey Museum (Box 63)
    - Kresge Research Building (Box 63)
    - LS&A Building (Box 63)
    - Law Quad (Box 63)
  - Washtenaw County
    - Calendars (Box 63)
    - Miscellaneous Brochures and Flyers (Box 63)
    - Indians (Box 63)
    - Maps (Box 63)
    - Dickson's Map 1896 (Box 63)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 63)
    - Museums (Box 63)
    - New York Building Tradition in Michigan (Box 63)
    - Nurseries (Box 63)
    - Officials and Politics (Box 63)
    - Organizations (Clubs) (Box 63)
    - Parks (Box 63)
    - Roads/Bridges (Box 63)
    - Delhi Bridge 2006 (Box 63)
    - Rural Preservation (Box 63)
    - Schools (Box 63)
    - Women (Box 63)
    - Eastern Michigan University 2008-2009 (Box 63)
    - Affordable Housing (Box 64)
    - Masons (Box 64)
    - General Information, 2 folders (Box 64)
    - Agriculture (Box 64)
    - Archaeology (Box 64)
    - Hometown Context 1935 (Box 64)
    - Architecture (Box 64)
    - Greek Revival (Box 64)
    - Cobblestone Buildings (Box 64)
    - Art Work 1983 (Box 64)
    - Council for the Arts (Box 64)
    - Atlas 1874 (Box 64)
    - Blacks (Box 64)
    - Builders (Box 64)
    - Business (Box 64)
    - Cemeteries (Box 64)
    - Centennial Farms (Box 64)
    - Churches (Box 64)
    - Consortium (Box 64)
    - Courthouse #3 (Box 64)
    - County Courthouse (Box 64)
    - Courts (Box 64)
    - Development/Planning (Box 64)
    - Directory 1878-1879 (Box 64)
    - County Fair (Box 65)
    - Genealogical Society (Box 65)
    - Germans (Box 65)
    - Proposal B Density and Development 2003 (Box 65)
    - Health (Box 65)
    - Historic Sites (Box 65)
    - History (Box 65)
    - Hospitals (Box 65)
    - Housing (Box 65)
    - Huron River (Box 65)
    - Mills (Box 65)
    - Mann Family (Box 65)
- Washtenaw County Historical Society
  The final series, Washtenaw County Historical Society documents the administrative and outreach functions of the society from 1981 to 2009. The series includes financial records, documents relating to the society's 150th anniversary, minutes, annual reports, and information on the opening and function of the Museum on Main Street (MOMS).
  - Exhibits 2000 (Box 65)
  - Programs (Box 65)
  - Impressions (Box 65)
  - Exhibit Photographs, 2003 (Box 65)
  - Programs 2003-2004 (Box 65)
  - Programs 2000-2002 (Box 65)
  - Consortium (Box 65)
  - Wander Washtenaw (Box 65)
  - 150th Anniversary (Box 65)
  - Historical Information for 150th Anniversary (Box 65)
  - Alice Cermglia Reports and Queries (Box 65)
  - Annual Meetings 2007-2008 (Box 65)
  - Annual Reports 2006-2007 (Box 65)
  - Beach Balls 1999 (Box 66)
  - Book (Proctor) (Box 66)
  - Board Meetings 2006-2008 (Box 66)
  - Board Members 2006-2007 (Box 66)
  - Brochure, 2 folders (Box 66)
  - Budget and Finance 2003-2009 (Box 66)
  - Bumper Sticker 2002 (Box 66)
  - Bylaws (Box 66)
  - Calendar 1986 (Box 66)
  - Collections (Box 66)
  - Exhibits 2007-2008 (Box 66)
  - Bidlack Ideas for Exhibits and Logos undated (Box 66)
  - Kitchen exhibit 2008 (Box 66)
  - Wedding/Exhibit Committee 2008 (Box 66)
  - Fundraising 2007-2008 (Box 66)
  - Gimmicks 1996-2008 (scattered) (Box 66)
  - Impressions General Information 2001-2008 (Box 66)
  - Index Impressions (Box 66)
  - History (Box 66)
  - Insurance (Box 66)
  - Membership (Box 66)
  - Minutes (Box 66)
  - Mission Statement (Box 66)
  - Pilgrimages 1981-1990 (Box 66)
  - Programs 2006-2008 (Box 66)
  - Museum on Main Street (MOMS) Photos 1989-1995 (Box 67)
  - History/Research MOMS (1015 Wall) (Box 67)
  - Maps and City Directories (Box 67)
  - General History (Box 67)
  - Oakley Correspondence (Box 67)
  - Greiner (Box 67)
  - Marz Family (Box 67)
  - Observer Article 1990 (Box 67)
  - Ruthruff Family (Box 67)
  - Kellogg/Warden Information (Box 67)
  - Correspondence w/Auburn, NY re: Kellogg-Warden (Box 67)
  - Dan Kellog Collection, letters, etc. (Box 67)
  - Video Tape, MOMS (Box 67)
  - Pauline Lists (Box 67)
  - Annual Meeting 2003-2004 (Box 67)
  - Annual Meeting 2001 (Box 67)
  - Annual Meeting 1999-2000 (Box 67)
  - Annual Reports (Box 67)
  - Appraisals Event 1998-2000 (Box 67)
  - Art Fair (Box 67)
  - Awards (Box 67)
  - Bach Estate (Box 67)
  - Pauline's Emails 2003 (Box 67)
  - Board Members (Box 67)
  - Board Meetings 2003 (Box 67)
  - Brochures (Box 67)
  - Budget (Box 67)
  - Business 2000 (Box 67)
  - Business 1999 (Box 67)
  - Business Support 2002-2003 (Box 67)
  - Business 2001-2002 (Box 67)
  - Business 1998 (Box 68)
  - Collections (Box 68)
  - Throw 2003 (Consortium) (Box 68)
  - Donations (Box 68)
  - Education Chair (Box 68)
  - Endowment (Box 68)
  - Exchanges with Historic Society (Box 68)
  - Janet Ferguson (Sunderland) (Box 68)
  - Fundraising (Box 68)
  - Grants (Box 68)
  - June Trip 2000-2001 (Box 68)
  - Knapp's Points, General Information (Box 68)
  - Loan Boxes (Box 68)
  - Membership 2001-2002 (Box 68)
  - Membership 1999-2000 (Box 68)
  - Doors of Ann Arbor, Karen O'Neal (Box 68)
  - Mohai Awards 2001 (Box 68)
  - Nominating (Box 68)
  - Pancake Breakfast (Box 68)
  - Program 1999-2000 (Box 68)
  - Publications List (Box 68)
  - Website (Box 68)
  - Directions for MOMS (Box 68)
  - Maria Wolff's MOMS Model (Box 68)
  - MOMS National Register Nomination (Box 68)
  - Photos 1995-2000 (Box 68)
  - MOMS Opening (Box 68)
  - MOMS Repairs (Box 68)
  - Investment Staff (Box 68)
  - McCauley Health System Archives 1992 (Box 68)
  - Ann Arbor Architecture (Box 69)
  - Ann Arbor and Michigan Calendars (Box 69)
  - Ann Arbor Ephemera (Box 69)
  - Ann Arbor Historic Preservation Awards (Box 69)
  - Ann Arbor Menus (Box 69)
  - Michigan Ephemera (Box 69)
  - Ann Arbor Posters (Folder 1)